这里是解决方案。在Utility类中，我们添加了
Here's the solution. In the Utility class, we add the
在代码片段中提供的辅助方法。我们也
helper methods that were provide in the gist. We also
在string.xml文件里对这些字符串进行了声明。在
declared these strings in the strings.xml file. In the
ForecastAdapter类的bindView方法中我们完成了
ForecastAdapter Class, in the bindView method, we finish off the
遗留下来的to do。从游标中读取最高气温值
remaining to do's. After we read the high temperature value
之后，我们试着找到ID为list_item_high_textview
from the cursor, we go and try to find the
所代表的TextView，
TextView, represented by the ID, list_item_high_textview
然后我使用Utility方法来格式化温度，
Then we use Utility function to format the temperature
这样它就可以被展示在TextView里。然后我们对
so that it can be displayed in the TextView. Then we do the
对最低气温值做同样的事情。在ForecastFragment类
same for the low temperature value. In the ForecastFragment class, in the on
的onCreateView方法中,我们去掉了SimpleCursorAdapter，作为替代，我们
onCreateView method, we remove the use of the simple cursor adapter. Instead, we
使用了ForecastAdapter并在listview上完成设置。
use the new ForecastAdapter and then we set it on the listview.